<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- XML file that handles all the text related to to the Psychologist
     Scene.
!-->
<room max_scenes="2">
  <scene-list>
    <initial type="conversation">
      <audio>access</audio>      
      <!-- Determines if any characters other than mc are in the scene!-->
      <actors>
	<is-empty>false</is-empty>
	<ryouko></ryouko>
      </actors>
      <opening>
	I brought up the idea of dreams to my neighbor, Ryouko a couple of days ago.
	I've always known Ryouko to be a Professor of Psychology at my university, and we've had some pleasant conversations about Psychology in the past.
	After finishing my Differential Equations course, I decided to stop by her office and ask her about it.
      </opening>
      <dialog>  
	[Ryouko] : "Hey, [John]!"
	[John] : "It's been a while, Professor Ryouko. How are things?"
	[Ryouko] : "Everything's going well. I just finished grading all of these papers."
	[Ryouko] : "This crop of students aren't quite as well as the last time I taught Intro to Psychology, and it shows in their papers." 
	[Ryouko] : "Most of them are C quality work, but there's some promising students in this bunch."
	[Ryouko] : "But enough about that. What can I do for you?"
	[John] : "I've got this weird question about dreams.
	[John] : "I know that you often talk about the history of Psychology."
	[John] : "We've discussed about both Sigmund Freud and Carl Yung's opinions on dreams and the human subconscious."
	[Ryouko] : "Yes. According to Freud, he believed that dreams represented a disguised form of fulfillment in a person's life.
	[Ryouko] : "These dreams can range from relatively Innocent behavior to behavior that would be considered illegal in our society."
	[Ryouko] : "However, these dreams may be what the person subconsciously wants but cannot obtain."
	[Ryouko] : "But I take that our conversation won't be about this?"
	(I nod.)
	[Ryouko] : "Is this going to take a long time to explain?"
	[John] : "It won't."
	[John] : "I've been having this dream where I've been teleported to this futuristic place."
	[John] : "Yet I feel like it's not. It's like a mixture of some futuristic room and 90s era technology."
	[John] : "And when I try to leave the room, I start to feel this pain that wakes me up from the dream."
	[John] : "Yet, I feel fine afterwards.
	[Ryouko] : "Hold on, I might have something that could help you with that."
	(Ryouko opens her desk drawers and begins to search for something.)
	(After a while, she finds something and hands it over to me.)
	[Ryouko] : "This could help with the pain that you experience in this dream."
	[John] : "What is this?"
	[Ryouko] : "It's a bottle of Codaprin, a type of painkiller. It's a little bit stronger than ibuprofen, but it shouldn't cause any problems for you."
	[John] : "Well, thanks."
	(Ryouko pauses for a moment and then begins to speak.)
	[Ryouko] : "So John, Tell me more about this place."
	[John] : "Well, It kinda looks like any ordinary hospital room, but with sleek steel walls."
	[John] : "There's also this retro and futuristic feel to this room too. I've noticed both these advanced indescribable tools that linger in the room."
	[John] : "But it also has those 90s era computers, you know, the ones with floppy disks and those small monitors."
	[John] : "I've also noticed that there's some magazines from that era. I think I saw a BYTE magazine or two.
	[John] : "It's almost as if its owner has some nostalgia for that time period."
	[Ryouko] : "Does this room have any windows or any small openings that you can peer out of?"
	[John] : "I think it does, but I've yet to look outside of them. My main focus was to simply get out the room."
	[Ryouko] : "And you've had this dream for how long?"
	[John] : "Almost two weeks."
	[Ryouko] : "Having the same dream or a variation of the same reason is nothing unique."
	[Ryouko] : "People suffering from mental trauma often talk about experiencing the same sort of events in their dreams."
	[Ryouko] : "For example, people suffering from PTSD often subconciously recreate the event.
	[Ryouko] : "Although, there's always some variation to the dream that they experience."
	[Ryouko] : "Since you've been having this dream for almost two weeks, You should try to explore more of the place."
	[Ryouko] : "This is of course, If you're telling the truth and not just trying to come up with some interesting story."
	[John] : "I wouldn't lie about something like this."
	[Ryouko] : "Well, try to look around for what I talked about. Maybe you'll be able to find something new. Make sure to take one of those painkillers I gave you, otherwise you won't be able to continue through."
	[John] : "I will. I'll see you later Ryouko."
      </dialog>
      <!-- Set the next scene and move to the next room. !-->
      <next-scene>scene1</next-scene>
      <!-- Move to next room!-->
      <next-room>apartment</next-room>
</initial>
<scene1>
  <audio>access</audio>
  <opening>
  </opening>
</scene1>

</scene-list>

</room>
