<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<room>
  <scene-list>
    <initial type="action">
      <audio>dream</audio>
      <opening>
	In front of me, I see a sleek, white corridor.
	Doors to various rooms litter the corridor and there seems to be something like a vending machine to the top right of me. I would buy something if I had any money...
	A large potted plant lays in the corner; its withered leaves are evident of a neglectful owner.
	I don't see anyone around, but judging from the condition of the corridor, it looks like people live there.
	I mean, there was the human-like poster in the hospital room.
	In any case, I should look around.
      </opening>

      <option-list>
	<option1>
	  <name>Head back to the hospital room</name>
	  <type>room-change</type>
	  <selection>
	    Head Back? Well, okay then. I doubt that I'll find anything new there, but just to be sure...
	  </selection>
	  <next-scene>initial</next-scene>
	  <next-room>xenon-hospital</next-room>
	</option1>
	<option2>
	  <name>Head to the door on the left</name>
	  <type>text</type>
	  <selection>
	    I first examine the door before attempting to open it.
	    There's a keypad to the left the door, but I don't know its combination.
	    I try to head into the door on the left by standing in front of it, but the door's window pane flashes dark red and then a beeping sound begins to play.
	    It doesn't seem as if I can enter this room.
	  </selection>
	</option2>

	<option3>
	  <name>Head to the door on the right</name>
	  <type>text</type>
	  <selection>
	    The keypad to the right of the door seems to suggest that I can't open this door through normal means.
	    When I stand in front of the door, a red color covers the door's window pane.
	    A beeping sound begins to play.
	    I don't think I can open this room, at least not yet.
	  </selection>
	</option3>

	<option4>
	  <name>Buy something from the vending machine</name>
	  <type>scene-change</type>
	  <selection>
	    I don't have any money to put in the.... Wait, there doesn't seem to be any place to put money on this machine.
	    Can't I just press any of the selection?
	    Oh shit... I don't need any money!
	    I decide to press a couple of random buttons, and several items pop out at the bottom, such as some drink in some bizarre bottle.
	    I quickly take a sip of the drink, and to my surprise, it tastes a bit like Dr. Pepper. How weird.
	    After filling my pockets, I decide to go back.
	  </selection>
	  <next-scene>day-one-ranfa</next-scene>
	  <next-room>xenon-leftcorridor</next-room>
	</option4>
      </option-list>
    </initial>
    
    <day-one-ranfa type="conversation">
      <audio>dream</audio>
      <actors>
	<is-empty>false</is-empty>
	<name>ranfa</name>
      </actors>
      <opening>
	As I return to the corridor, I notice the sound of footsteps, and then the door to the left room slides open. In front of me... a woman with green hair.
	Wait, green hair? I take another glance at her. Green fluffy hair, golden eyes, large bows to the side, and a rather revealing outfit.
	After some awkward moments, she opens her mouth to speak.
	Some bizarre language comes out of her mouth, and after realizing that I can't understand a word she says, she opens her mouth again. I immediately recognize it as English, although with an bizarre accent.
      </opening>
      <dialog>
[???]:  "Who are you?"
[John]: "My name is John."
[???]: "Where did you come from?"
[John]: "I came from that hospital room in the back."
[???]: "..."
[???]: "I'm not fond of jokes. Where did you come from?"
[John]: "I'm from Earth. I don't know what this place is, I don't know where this place is, and I have no idea idea who you are. I thought this station was abandoned and so I decided to look around."
[???]: "Earth?"
[John]: "Yes, it's a planet."
[???]: "..."
[???]: "How were you able to get out of the hospital room?"
[John]: "I don't know."
[???]: "..."
[John]: "Now it's your turn. Who are you?"
[???]: "???"
[John]: "I said, who are you?"
[???]: "My name is Ranfa."
[John]: "Ranfa."
[Ranfa]: "Yes, Ranfa. Is there a problem?"
[John]: "Well, I've never heard of anyone named Ranfa."
[Ranfa]: "..."
[John]: "Can I ask you a question?"
[Ranfa]: "Go ahead."
[John]: "Any reason why you're wearing that?"
[Ranfa]: "Wearing what?"
[John]: "That outfit of yours."
[Ranfa]: "I normally wear this. Is there something wrong with that?"
[John]: "Err...No, not at all."
[Ranfa]: "Any other questions?"
[John]: "What is this place?"
[Ranfa]: "This is the spaceship Xenon."
[John]: "How big is this spaceship?"
[Ranfa]: "The vessel is quite spacious. Its exact dimensions are classified."
[John]: "Whose spaceship is this?"
[Ranfa]: "It belongs to Bianca, the captain."
[John]: "Where is this Bianca?"
[Ranfa]: "That information is also classified."
[John]: "Is she close by at least?"
[Ranfa]: "...Perhaps."
[John]: "Where is this spaceship located?"
[Ranfa]: "This spaceship is currently in orbit of the star Roldan.
[John]: "Roldan?"
[Ranfa]: "Yes, Roldan. It's a rather diminutive red dwarf star, hostile to almost all form of life."
[John]: ("I have never heard of a star called Roldan. But it's fairly obvious that I'm quite far away from the Solar System.)
[John]: ("Also, why is she being so specific?")
[John]: (I clear my throat.)
[John]: "What is the spaceship Xenon doing on Roldan.?"
[Ranfa]: "Captain Bianca is the only one that can answer that."
[John]: "Can you show me the rest of this ship? I would like to know how this place looks like."
[Ranfa]: "I'm afraid that most of the doors in this spaceship are locked to me. The only doors open are the observatory room and the hanger."
[John]: "Why are you telling me this?"
[Ranfa]: "..."
[John]: "Wait, so you don't consider me a threat? Is that why you're telling me?"
[Ranfa]: "You have no weapons, and I can easily dispatch you should you try something."
[John]: ("She brandishes a pistol.")
[John]: "Well, may I look around in those rooms?"
[Ranfa]: "..."
[Ranfa]: "You can browse both rooms, but should you try anything, I and the Automatic Defense system will destroy you."
[John]: "Harsh words from a girl dressed like a stripper."
[Ranfa]: "..."
(Ranfa walks off, leaving me to explore.)
      </dialog>
      
      <next-scene>day-one-end</next-scene>
      <next-room>xenon-rightcorridor</next-room>
    </day-one-ranfa>
    
    <day-one-end type="action">
      <audio></audio>
      <opening>I'm back in the left corridor.</opening>
      <option-list>
	<option1>
	  <name>Go to the right corridor</name>
	  <type>room-change</type>
	  <selection>
	    Yeah, let's go back.
	  </selection>
	  <next-scene>day-one-end</next-scene>
	  <next-room>xenon-rightcorridor</next-room>
	</option1>
	
	<option2>
	  <name>Go to the hospital room</name>
	  <type>room-change</type>
	  <selection>
	    Go back to the hospital room?
	  </selection>
	  <next-scene>day-one-end</next-scene>
	  <next-room>xenon-hospital</next-room>
	</option2>

	<option3>
	  <name>Use the vending machine</name>
	  <type>text</type>
	  <selection>
	    I don't need anymore soda or junk food right now. Really, I don't.
	  </selection>
	</option3>

	<option4>
	  <name>Go to the door on the left.</name>
	  <type>text</type>
	  <selection>
	    Ranfa came from this room, but I don't have the combination to the keypad. I can't go inside.
	  </selection>
	</option4>

	<option5>
	  <name>Go to the door on the right</name>
	  <type>text</type>
	  <selection>
	    Since I don't know the number combination for the keypad, I can't go inside the room.
	  </selection>
	</option5>
      </option-list>
    </day-one-end>

    
  </scene-list>
</room>
