<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<room>
  <scene-list>
    <!-- ##################################################!-->
    <!-- Day 1 Scenes                                      !-->
    <!-- ##################################################!-->
    
    <initial type="conversation">
      <audio>dream</audio>
      <actors>
	<is-empty>true</is-empty>
      </actors>
      <opening>
	After spending an hour or so on homework, I decide to take one of the pills Ruyoko gave me and head off to bed.
	
	I wake up to the familiar scene that I've experienced for the last two weeks.
	A Hospital room, both futuristic and retro. I'm in the same hospital bed that I always wake up.
	The same chocolate bed sheets and the same silky green pillowcase.
	The floor and the walls are as sleek as ever, bring up memories of the inside of a spaceship.
	The 90s era computer is still there, and I decide to boot the bad boy up.
	Sounds of a hard-disk moving fill the room, and the CRT monitor displays the all-too familiar IBM logo.
	After waiting for a bit, the phrase "UNIX" appears, alongside the current date and the login prompt.
	I notice the date. "Saturday, September 19, 1992." Almost fifth-teen years ago.
	I look around the bookshelf and see again the 90s era magazines and newspapers.
	There's also a shelf dedicated to something advanced, but it's written in a language I've never seen before.
	Now that you think about, almost everything else in this room is written in that language.
	The only thing that's in English is the computer and a couple of magazines. Pretty strange.

	I look for the all familiar windows that I talked about with Professor Ryouko, and see one at the far right of the room.
	The blinds are shut and after opening I see what appears to be my reflection.... and something dark.
	In fact, it's almost pitch dark, save a few bright... stars?

	
      </opening>
      <dialog>
	I look again to verify what I saw, and see again the bright stars that dot the landscape.
      </dialog>
      <next-scene>scene1</next-scene>
      <next-room>xenon-hospital</next-room>
    </initial>
    <scene1 type="action">
      <audio>realize</audio>
      <opening>
	[John]: "I'm in space. God, why didn't I search this room earlier?"
	[John]: "There has to be some form of artificial gravity which allows me to walk normally here."
	(I peer again at the landscape and notice the reddish tint of the star.)
	(This obviously isn't our sun, since our sun is bright orange, and I don't notice any planets orbiting the star.)
	(In fact, I believe this ship is the only thing orbiting it.)
	(How far away is this place from Earth or our Solar System?)
	(In any case, I should try to examine my surroundings again.)	
      </opening>

      <option-list>
	<option1>
	  <name>Examine PC</name>
	  <type>text</type>
	  <selection>
	    [John]: "Yeah, let's see what we can find out of this machine."
	    The login prompt is the same as it was a couple of minutes ago.
	    It also displays the date, which is Saturday, September 19, 1992.
	    For whatever reason, the username is automatically set to the  user 'ranfa',
	    but since I don't know the password, I can't get in.
	    I can try to make a new account, but there's not much of a point.
	    (I decide to step away from the PC.)
	  </selection>
	</option1>
	<option2>
	  <name>Look out the window again</name>
	  <type>text</type>
	  <selection>
	    I look out the window again and see a part of the spaceship and the red star that it orbits.
	    I believe this type of star is called a "Red Dwarf".
	    They're fairly common in space, but they don't make good candidates for life to survive.
	    I think it was something involving radiation or something?
	  </selection>
	</option2>
	<option3>
	  <name>Leave the room</name>
	  <type>room-change</type>
	  <selection>
	    I look at the futuristic door that bars me from the rest of the spaceship.
	    In my previous dreams, every time I tried to exit the room, I would start to feel pain across my body that would wake me up.
	    That's the reason why Professor Ryouko give me these pills, but I still feel hesitant to even get close to the damn thing.
	    After thinking about it for a couple of minutes, I decide to exit the room.
	    I slowly make my way to the door, bracing myself for the pain that follows.
	    But the pain never arrives, in fact, I don't feel a thing.
	    [John]: "It has to be the painkillers that Ryouko gave me."
	    There's no doorknob, but the doors opens from the right, leaving me open to explore.
	    I decide to leave this room.
	  </selection>	    
	  <next-scene>day-one-last</next-scene>
	  <next-room>xenon-leftcorridor</next-room>
	</option3>
      </option-list>
    </scene1>
    
    <day-one-last type="action">
      <audio>dream</audio>
      <opening>I return back to the hospital room.</opening>
      <option-list>
	<option1>
	  <name>Leave the hospital room.</name>
	  <type>room-change</type>
	  <selection>
	    Yeah, there was no point coming back to this room.
	  </selection>
	  <next-scene>day-one-last</next-scene>
	  <next-room>xenon-leftcorridor</next-room>
	</option1>

	<option2>
	  <name>Examine the PC</name>
	  <type>text</type>
	  <selection>
	    There's not much I can do with this PC. I know that it tries to login using the user 'ranfa', but I don't know the password. Who the hell is Ranfa?
	  </selection>
	</option2>

	<option3>
	  <name>Look outside the window</name>
	  <type>text</type>
	  <selection>
	    I can't believe that I'm on some starship orbiting some star somewhere in the galaxy. That's so surreal.
	  </selection>
	</option3>
      </option-list>
    </day-one-last>
    
    <!-- ##################################################!-->
    <!-- Day 2 Scenes                                      !-->
    <!-- ##################################################!-->
    
    <day2-initial>
      <audio>dream</audio>
      <opening>
	I awake once more in the hospital room onboard the spaceship Xenon.
      </opening>
    </day2-initial>
    <day1>
    </day1>
  </scene-list>
</room>
