<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<room>
  <scene-list>
    <initial type="conversation">
      <audio>nil</audio>      
      <actors>
	<is-empty>true</is-empty>
      </actors>

      <opening>
As soon as I enter the room, I quickly notice how different it is from the rest of the rooms that I've visited. The dark-tint of the room contrasts with the light white of the corridor, and the three pods in from of me are labeled with a specific number. Suddenly, I notice a soft beeping sound from behind the middle coffin, and I look at the blank computer terminal at the back, waiting for any user input.
      </opening>
      <dialog>
	Suddenly, I hear something moving. I turn around and see Ranfa's familiar face.
      </dialog>
      <next-scene>day1-ranfa</next-scene>
      <next-room>xenon-cryogenic</next-room>
    </initial>

    <day1-ranfa type="conversation">
      <audio>encoder</audio>
      <actors>
	<is-empty>false</is-empty>
	<name>ranfa</name>
      </actors>
      <opening>
	[John]: "Ranfa? Where the hell have you been?"
	Instead of answering my question, She puts her index finger to her mouth and points in the direction of the computer terminal.
	I look at the screen once again and see that the screen saver is just starting up.
	Then, a message pops up on the terminal. It reads:
	P.P.E
	Psychic Program Encoder
	PSY Encoder operating...
	[John]: "What the hell is a Psychic Program Encoder?"
	[Ranfa]: "It's a invention that allows people to traverse through the void that binds."
	[John]: "The void that binds? What the hell do you mean?"
	(Just as Ranfa opens her mouth to speak, a piercing warning sound goes off in the room. The middle capsule flashes white for several seconds, and then opens completely. A red-haired woman lies dormant inside of the capsule, surrounded by various machines and sensors of unknown origin. These sensors cover her nude body, and a black visor covers her eyes.
      </opening>
      <dialog>
	[John]: "...What the hell?"
	[John]: "Ranfa, why the hell is there someone in this capsule? Do you know this person?"
	[Ranfa]: "You don't know?"
	[John]: "Of course I don't!"
	(In a soft quiet voice, I hear Ranfa mutter something.)
	[Ranfa]: "Falneria...."
	(Is this person's name Falneria? It has to be.)
	(I look back at the capsule and quickly notice something.)
	(The girl starts to squirm in the capsule, as if she's in some nightmare.)
	(The tossing and turning becomes more and more frantic, and some of the sensors come off from her body.)
	(With a quick jolt, she sits up and takes off her visor.)
	(I open my mouth.)
	[John]: "Hey! Is your name Falneria?"
	(Ranfa looks at me with a look of disapproval, but then the girl responds.)
	[???]: "Ranfa, how did he get here?"
	(I look at Ranfa.)
	[Ranfa]: "He can traverse through the void that binds."
	(The void that binds?)
	[Falneria]: "Is he a freecaster?"
	[Ranfa]: "I do not know."
	(Falneria looks at me.)
	[Falneria]: "You! From what planet do you come from?"
	[John]: "Earth. I come from Earth."
	[John]: "It orbits the sun... I mean the star Sol."
	[John]: "Do you know how far this place is from my solar system?"
	(Falneria pauses for a moment before speaking)
	[Falneria]: "I do not know of where this... Sol is located.
	I also have not heard of a planet called Earth.
	In fact, judging by your appearance, I was going to ask if you were from Aeora."
	[John]: "I've never heard of an planet named Aeora."
	But as Falneria begins to speak, I feel a sharp pain at my side and it quickly spreads to the rest of my body.
	Ranfa immediately notices and tries to hold up my body, but it's no use.
	I fall down to the ground, unable to move without feeling tremendous pain.
	The pain subsides and then I awake on the floor, in a room I recognize as my own.
      </dialog>
      <next-scene>end</next-scene>
      <next-room>save-point</next-room>
    </day1-ranfa>
    
    <end type="conversation">
    </end>
  </scene-list>
</room>
